

Contact

Saudi Arabia

Cell No. & Watsapp +966582713664 (Mobile) s.khan@2035skills.com 2035skills@gmail.com

YouTube Channel

https://www.youtube.com/cha nnel/UCqpm12iorlb1hzf9YF6kag

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/shakeel-khan-5391031a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Team Management
New Business Development
Training & Certification Management
Lead Generation
Managerial Skill
Hosting
Channel Operations
Blog Writer
Trainer Soft Skills & H.S.E

Languages

ENGLISH, ARABIC, URDU, HINDI, PUNJABI, PUSHTO AND PAHARI

Certifications

Digital Marketing Associate-SCDM-A™
Corporate Sales Associate-SCCS-A™
Certified Scrum Fundamentals-SFC™
Marketing Research Associate-SCMR-A™
Marketing Strategy Associate-SCMS-A™
Six Sigma Yellow Belt Professional
H2S Train the Trainer
IOSH Working Safely
Sales Skills Enhancement Program-SSEP
Finance for Non-Finance Managers
Business Transformations & Change
Management

Shakeel Ahmed Khan,

SCCS-A™, SCDM-A™, SCMR-A™, SCMS-A™, SFC-A™ and Six Sigma Yellow Belt Professional.

2035 Skills - Authorized Training Partner, (V.A.T.P - VMEdu) at VMEdu Inc., Al-Khobar, Saudi Arabia.

Summary

Having +25 years of experience in Training, sales, marketing, office administrations / management, operations, recruitment, accounts/finance,etc. I count with the following characteristics: Outgoing, leadership, staff management, good handling in the development of friendly and respectful relationships. Listening skills, and force sales administration, sales closing with many types of customers, negotiation skills with a lot of initiative to solve problems efficiently and achieve the goals set by the company.

Loves to face challenges, and always having inventory attitude towards the satisfaction of my executives and organization. A confident and self-motivated professional of business development and management experience, Marketing, having dealt with senior decision makers from industries including Oil & Gas, Manufacturing, Construction, Ministries, Telecommunication, Banking and Finance, Heavy Industries etc.

A good team leader with excellent leadership qualities, very passionate about my job, and quick to learn. Skills in business development, marketing and communications, that I have acquired over the years coupled with my eagerness to learn and adapt to new tools and methods have enabled me to excel in my career.

Experience

2035 Skills - VMEdu Inc. Authorized Training Partner, (V.A.T.P - VMEdu) November 2021 - Present (3 months), G.C.C & MENAT Region.

This is my own portal where we are having 700+ trainings with International Certifications.

Nawyel Group

Director, Training Division 2035skills (Nawyel Group) October 2014 - Present (7 years 4 months)

Al-Khobar, Saudi Arabia, Karachi-Pakistan, Durban-South Africa and North Carolina-USA

Planning, Designing, arranging, delivering all sorts of Soft Skill, Hard Skill, HSE, Certification courses, Public Events and In-House trainings, doing recruitment, selection, analysing and Interviewing staff and manpower for our clients.

MARCUSEVANS, PAKISTAN SERNIOR CLIENT ACQUISTION OFFICER November 2008 - November 2014 (6 years 1 month) PAKISTAN

Career-wise:

- 1.Thorough research of the market and industry knowledge to develop the syllabus, Communicate and collaborate with the top management of GCC market leader for endorsement and delegations to the events.
- 2. Assign and manage sales target and their achievements through.
- 3.Lead a dedicated sales team for each event.
- 4.Manage marketing communications (newsletter designing and content writing), social media and CRM issues.

Project Summary

I had successfully led +50 events in GCC market, of Finance, legal, Construction and Projects Management, social media, Budgeting, Administration, higher Management etc.

Faxsol Pakistan MANAGER OPERATIONS April 2000 - October 2008 (8 years 7 months)

Supervision of Business Administration, Financial Consultancy, Manpower suppliers, Loan and Leasing Consultancy, Heavy Machinery Supplying (Purchasing/Sales/Rentals).

ERUM OVERSEAS EMPLOYMENT EXCHANGE RECRUITMENT / OPERATION MANAGER

July 1994 - July 2000 (6 years 1 month)

Worked as Recruitment and Operations Manager, responsible for Selection of manpower, arranging there selection test, interviews, documentations, visa arrangement, government relations works, Supplied Manpower to many Multinational organizations of Saudi Arabia, U.A..E, Qatar, Kuwait, Bahrain, Libya, Iran, Iraq, Brunei, Korea, Japan U.K to diversify Industries, like medical, para medical, construction, Mechanical, Electrical, power, Oil and gas industries, Government Organizations, Forces, technical, non-technical, un-skilled, semi qualified, highly qualified, more or less in all fields.

GULF EVENT MANAGEMENT, ABU DHABI, U.A.E. PROGRAMME ADMINISTRATOR

January 1990 - June 1994 (4 years 6 months)

Designing, Planning and Conducting conferences, trainings and workshops as per the market needs and requirements, also arranging the expeditions, stage programmes, concerts of world-famous artists at all G.C.C countries.

ERUM OVERSEAS EMPLOYMENT EXCHANGE RECRUITMENT and Public Relation Officer.

September 1986 - December 1989 (3 years 4 months)

Worked as Recruitment and Operations Manager, responsible for Selection of manpower, arranging their selection test, interviews, documentations,

visa arrangement, government relations work, Supplied Manpower to many many Multinational organizations of Saudi Arabia, U.A..E, Qatar, Kuwait, Bahrain, Libya, Iran, Iraq, Brunei, Korea, Japan U.K to diversify Industries, like medical, para medical, construction, Mechanical, Electrical, power, Oil and gas

industries, Government Organizations, Forces, technical, non-technical, un skilled, semi qualified, highly qualified, more or less in all fields.

Education

Karachi University

B.B.A, Marketing, Banking · (1987 - 1990)

National College of Arts and Science, Karachi-Pakistan.

Intermediate in Commerce Subjects, (1984 – 1987)

Dehli Mercantile Society Secondary School, Karachi-Pakistan.

T.S.C, TECHNICAL · (1982 - 1984)

Conducted Trainings as a Trainer: -

- 1. Basic First Aid and CPR
- 2. Basic Fire Fighting
- 3. Basic Fireman
- 4. Fire Rescue
- 5. Defensive Driving
- 6. Fork lift Safety
- 7. Fork Lift Operation
- 8. Manual Handling
- 9. H2S & SCBA
- 10. Working at Height
- 11. Fall Protection
- 12. Electrical Safety
- 13. Work Permit Receiver
- 14. Log out Tag out (LOTO)
- 15. Confined Space Entry
- 16. Confined Space Rescue
- 17. Safety Risk Assessment
- 18. Hot and Cold Work

And many other HSE trainings.

Conducted Soft Skill Trainings as a Trainer: -

- 1. Digital Marketing
- 2. Marketing Research
- 3. Marketing Strategy
- 4. Corporate Sales
- 5. Tele-Marketing
- 6. Managerial Skills
- 7. Supervisory Skills
- 8. Time Management
- Interpersonal Skills
 Anger Management
 - And many other Soft Skill Trainings.

Current Status:

Recently I am in Pakistan looking for any opportunity.